Guide to the Robert J. Leach papers, 1930-1998
Leach, Robert J. papers, 1930-1998
- "ELISHA BATES, 1817-1827. THE INFLUENCE OF AN EARLY OHIO PUBLISHER UPON QUAKER REFORM." An Abstract Presented for the Degree of Master of Arts by RJL, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- "QUAKERISM AND GOVERNMENT: A study of Quaker political experience from 1914 to 1955" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 55-56)
- "Medieval Civilization" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 57)
- "Life and Teachings of Jesus of Nazareth" by RJL (Box 18, Folder 58)
- "A SHORT HISTORY OF NORTH CAROLINA, Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends," by RJL (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Books I and II of Mary K Leach, Trip to Europe, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Volume Six: Commentary on Autobiography for 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
- Autobiography: Sixth Section, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Autobiography: Eighth Section, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
- RJL Journal, Volume 54, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- RJL Journal, Volume 55: 2nd-9th Months, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Autobiography: Part Nine, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- RJL Journal, Volume 57 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- RJL Journal, Volume 58 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- RJL Journal, Volume 59, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- RJL Journal, Volume 60 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- RJL Journal, Volume 61, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- RJL Journal, Volume 62, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Index Update, A-J, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, A-J (Box 19, Folder 17-29)